To write the convert_grades function I'll first write a function that
لكتابة الدالة convert_grades سأكتبُ أولاً دالة تحول
converts a single grade, and
درجة فردية
then I can apply that function to the entire data frame.
ثم يمكنني تطبيق تلك الدالة على .إطار البيانات بالكامل
I'll call the singular version of the function convert_grade.
وسأستدعي النسخة الفردية من .الدالة convert_grade
I wrote this function using a series of if statements.
لقد كتبتُ هذه الدالة باستخدام .متسلسلة من عبارات if
First, if the grade was at least 90 then I returned A,
أولاً، إذا كانت الدرجة 90 على الأقل فقد أرجعتُ الدرجة A، وإذا كانت الدالة 80 على
then if the grade was at least 80 I returned B and so on.
الأقل، فقد أرجعتُ الدرجة B .وهكذا
Now I'll try this function out on a few single values.
والآن سأجرب هذه الدالة .على قيم قليلة فردية
If I convert the grade 80, I get B.
.إذا حولتُ الدرجة 80، فسأحصل على الدرجة B
And if I convert 79, I get C, which is what I expected.
،وإذا حولتُ الدرجة 79، فسأحصل على الدرجة C .وهو ما توقعته
Next I can use the applymap function
وبعد ذلك، يمكنني استخدام الدالة applymap
to call the convert_grade function on each element of the data frame.
لاستدعاء الدالة convert_grade .بكل عنصر من إطار البيانات
Now I'll call this function on the example grid's data frame and
والآن، سأستدعي هذه الدالة بإطار بيانات الشبكة المثال
it looks like it worked.
.ويبدو أنها قد نجحت